Finding Aid for the Barbara Ann Conlogue Collection of Eleanor Steber Photographs and Clippings, circa 1935-1990
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Slides, 1958-circa 1970, II.; Item 177-374
  - Eleanor Steber in costume with unidentified girl on her lap, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-279)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-280)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie from Wozzeck backstage with Gordon Andrews, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-281)
  - Eleanor Steber in conversation with unidentified man with his back to the camera, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-282)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna in Don Giovanni at the Metropolitan Opera, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-283)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca from Tosca on stage, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-284)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca from Tosca on stage, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-285)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca from Tosca on stage bowing, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-286)
  - Eleanor Steber with soprano Lucine Amara, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-287)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese from Rosenkavalier backstage, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-288)
  - Eleanor Steber with unidentified woman, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-289)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca from Tosca on stage, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-290)
  - Eleanor Steber and Gordon Andrews, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-291)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca from Tosca on stage, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-292)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca and Leonard Warren as Campora taking bows on stage during a performance of Tosca, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-293)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca from Tosca on stage, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-294)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca from Tosca on stage, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-295)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca from Tosca on stage, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-296)
  - Eleanor Steber taking bow on stage with three other performers, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-297)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca from Tosca on stage, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-298)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-299)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-300)
  - Eleanor Steber with pianist Edwin Biltcliffe and husband Gordon Andrews (in uniform), with Helen Ulmer seated in navy-colored dress, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-301)
  - Eleanor Steber with husband Gordon Andrews in line for food, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-302)
  - Eleanor Steber in line for food, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-303)
  - Eleanor Steber and two unidentified women in line for food, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-304)
  - Eleanor Steber with unidentified man and others in a restaurant or cafeteria, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-305)
  - Eleanor Steber, holding scrapbook, with unidentified woman, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-306)
  - Eleanor Steber in group shot, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-307)
  - Eleanor Steber, seated, in group shot, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-308)
  - Eleanor Steber and Gordon Andrews with projector, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-309)
  - Eleanor Steber and Gordon Andrews near projector screen, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-310)
  - Eleanor Steber and Gordon Andrews near projector screen, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-311)
  - Eleanor Steber and Gordon Andrews near projector screen, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-312)
  - Eleanor Steber near projector screen, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-313)
  - Eleanor Steber near projector screen, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-314)
  - Eleanor Steber with unidentified women at social event, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-315)
  - Eleanor Steber performing in recital with unidentified accompanist, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-316)
  - Eleanor Steber taking bow onstage, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-317)
  - Eleanor Steber performing in recital with unidentified accompanist, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-318)
  - Eleanor Steber performing in recital with unidentified accompanist, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-319)
  - Eleanor Steber, holding bouquet, taking bow after recital, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-320)
  - Eleanor Steber, with bouquet, performing in recital with unidentified accompanist, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-321)
  - Eleanor Steber performing in recital with unidentified accompanist, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-322)
  - Eleanor Steber, with bouquet, performing in recital with unidentified accompanist, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-323)
  - Image too dark to identify content, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-324)
  - Image of large oval-shaped painted portrait of Eleanor Steber, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-325)
  - Social gathering on the patio of Eleanor Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-326)
  - Eleanor Steber, seated, on the patio at her home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-327)
  - Eleanor Steber and unidentified woman at a gathering at Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-328)
  - Eleanor Steber and unidentified woman at a gathering at Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-329)
  - Eleanor Steber with Margaret Ulmer (left), and an unidentified woman at a gathering at Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-330)
  - Eleanor Steber, unidentified woman, child, and dog seated at a gathering at Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-331)
  - Eleanor Steber with two unidentified women at a gathering at Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-332)
  - Eleanor Steber with Leonard Brownstein at a gathering at Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-333)
  - Eleanor Steber with unidentified man at a gathering at Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-334)
  - Eleanor Steber, husband Gordon Andrews, brother William Steber (right), and others at a gathering at Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-335)
  - Eleanor Steber, Barbara Ann Conlogue, and a dog at a gathering at Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-336)
  - Eleanor Steber, husband Gordon Andrews, brother William Steber (right), and company at a gathering at Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-337)
  - Eleanor Steber, husband Gordon Andrews, brother William Steber (right), at a gathering at Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-338)
  - Eleanor Steber, husband Gordon Andrews, brother William Steber (far right), and company at a gathering at Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-339)
  - Eleanor Steber, husband Gordon Andrews, brother William Steber (far right), and company at a gathering at Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-340)
  - Eleanor Steber, husband Gordon Andrews, brother William Steber (far right), and company at a gathering at Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, 1962, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-341)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie from Wozzeck on stage, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-342)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie from Wozzeck on stage, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-343)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie from Wozzeck on stage, bows, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-344)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie from Wozzeck on stage, bows, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-345)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie from Wozzeck on stage, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-346)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie from Wozzeck on stage, bows, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-347)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie from Wozzeck on stage, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-348)
  - Eleanor Steber recital with orchestra, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-349)
  - Eleanor Steber recital with orchestra, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-350)
  - Eleanor Steber recital with orchestra, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-351)
  - Eleanor Steber recital with orchestra, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-352)
  - Eleanor Steber recital with orchestra, bows, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-353)
  - Eleanor Steber recital with orchestra, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-354)
  - Eleanor Steber recital with orchestra, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-355)
  - Eleanor Steber recital with orchestra, bows, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-356)
  - Eleanor Steber recital with orchestra, bows, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-357)
  - Eleanor Steber recital with orchestra, bows, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-358)
  - Eleanor Steber recital with orchestra, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-359)
  - Eleanor Steber recital with orchestra, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-360)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital, pink dress, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-361)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital, pink dress, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-362)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital, pink dress, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-363)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital, pink dress, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-364)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital, pink dress, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-365)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital, pink dress, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-366)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital, pink dress, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-367)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital with unidentified accompanist, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-368)
  - Eleanor Steber and unidentified accompanist taking bows, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-369)
  - Eleanor Steber on stage, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-370)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital with unidentified accompanist, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-371)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital with unidentified accompanist, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-372)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital with unidentified accompanist, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-373)
  - Eleanor Steber with bouquets of flowers, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-374)
- Clippings, 1952-1990, III.; Item 375-380
  Arranged in chronological order.
  - Postcard from Steber to Conlogue from Paris, 22 September 1952 (Box 2, Item 375)
    Photograph of Eiffel Tower.
  - Greater Lowell music lovers laud Eleanor Steber concert, 21 November 1966, In Lowell Sun, p. 16. (Box 2, Item 376)
    Review of recital at Liberty Hall, Lowell, Massachusetts, with photographs of Steber, her accompanist Edwin Biltcliffe, and Lowell residents, Barbara Conlogue, Hugh Downey, and Cathy Mirras.
  - Eleanor Steber program for performance at New England Conservatory, 27 February 1977, Inscribed to Barbara [Conlogue]. (Box 2, Item 377)
  - Steber's Mozart night of nostalgia, 1 March 1977, In Boston Herald. (Box 2, Item 378)
    Review by Ellen Pfeifer of Steber recital held at New England Conservatory 27 February 1977.
  - Still, and always, a diva, undated, In Boston Globe. (Box 2, Item 379)
    Review by Richard Dyer of Steber recital held at New England Conservatory 27 February 1977.
  - Eleanor Steber's golden voice and generous heart, 6 October 1990, In Boston Globe. (Box 2, Item 380)
    Obituary by Richard Dyer.
  - Eleanor Steber, at 76; former Met prima donna, undated, Obituary, in The Record. (Box 2, Item 381)
  - Farewell to Steber, 8 December 1990, In Opera News. (Box 2, Item 382)
    Obituary by Harvey Phillips.
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
Sopranos (Singers)--United States--Photographs; Opera--Photographs; Steber, Eleanor--Photographs
Genres
Portraits; Black-and-white photographs; Color photographs; Color slides; Clippings (information artifacts)
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
J. Warren Perry Collection of Photographs
Mus. Arc. 3.1
This collection of 2110 photographs contains 26 photographs of Eleanor Steber. The collection is also available in UBdigit.